

About me

Hey, I am a highly skilled and enthusiastic UI/UX Designer with 5 years and 10 months of experience. I mainly focus on creating mind-blowing website designs and make sure people enjoy these to the fullest in the first looks and connect with their hearts.

Skill Sets

- > HTML | HTML 5
- BEM
- > CSS | CSS 3
- Gitlab
- > SASS/SCSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Gulp

Capabilites

- UI/UX Mobile/Web
- > Front end Development
- CSS3 Animation
- > PSD to HTML
- Responsive HTML

Experience

5 Years & 10 months of experience

Software Engineer

Opentrends Technologies Pvt Ltd

Indeevaram Infopark Thrissur January 2021 - Present

UI / UX Developer

Times World Media and Technology Solutions Pvt Ltd

Govt. Cyberpark Calicut, Kerala April 2019 - December 2020

UI Developer

Netstager Technologies Pvt Ltd

Calicut, Kerala January 2017 - March 2019

Web Developer

Quince It Solutions

Calicut, Kerala January 2016 – December 2016

Web Designer

xltechnologies

Calicut, Kerala

June 2015 – December 2015

Softwares









Education

Graduate

B.com with co-operation, Calicut University 2014 (70% Marks)

H.S.E

Govt. Higher Secondary School Koduvally 2011 (73% Marks)

SSLC

Sacred Heart Higher Secondary School Thiruvambady 2009 (75% Marks)

Web Designing

O2 Web Academy Kallai Road Calicut, Kerala

Personal Information

Full Name

Sreedarsh CP

Date of Birth

13 July 1994

Languages

English, Malayalam, Hindi

Marital Status

Single

Contact

Mail - sreedarshcp@gmail.com Mobile - 9645 36 90 82

My Works

www.cplondonthecity.co.uk

www.surfacell.com

www.7harvestme.com

www.deshabhimani.com

www.ksidc.org

www.hammadionline.com

www.sasthapurihotels.com

www.remoteteam.ch

www.akay-group.com

www.engagedxb.gov.ae

www.funboothdubai.com

www.makaremhotels.com

www.agorsagourmet.com

www.hotelgrandnoor.com

www.bec-me.com

www.crabiz.com









